B2.
Toby is calling his mum to tell her about lunch at Sunshine Middle School.
Listen to their conversation and complete the notes below. Hi, Mum.
Let me tell you about lunchtime here at Sunshine Middle School. It's amazing! Really?
What makes it amazing?
First of all, here we get an hour and a half for lunch.
So there's lots of time to eat a good lunch and then relax for a while before afternoon lessons.
The dining hall is great, and every day there are different dishes.
We can eat delicious hot food and stay healthy.
There are many meats and vegetables and different kinds of noodles.
They taste really good.
And then I can try all kinds of local snacks. They're delicious!
And I know how to eat with chopsticks now.
Oh, we even get to watch movies after we eat.
It's a cool way to relax during lunchtime.
I'm glad to hear that.
Enjoy your time there!